{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007380851","data":{"timestamp":" 947007380851"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007426822","data":{"timestamp":" 947007426821"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007426897","data":{"timestamp":" 947007426897"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 9c83c4a3-d415-46e6-be5e-c135be4dbaa4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007461884","data":{"timestamp":" 947007461884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007476942","data":{"timestamp":" 947007476942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007489421","data":{"timestamp":" 947007489420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007505183","data":{"timestamp":" 947007505183"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007519933","data":{"timestamp":" 947007519933"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007528781","data":{"timestamp":" 947007528781"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007539248","data":{"timestamp":" 947007539248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007551714","data":{"timestamp":" 947007551714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007566378","data":{"timestamp":" 947007566377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007577667","data":{"timestamp":" 947007577667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007590667","data":{"timestamp":" 947007590667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007603650","data":{"timestamp":" 947007603649"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007615408","data":{"timestamp":" 947007615408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007615589","data":{"timestamp":" 947007615589"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007627186","data":{"timestamp":" 947007627185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007639171","data":{"timestamp":" 947007639171"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007650428","data":{"timestamp":" 947007650428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007661974","data":{"timestamp":" 947007661974"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007674767","data":{"timestamp":" 947007674766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007688237","data":{"timestamp":" 947007688237"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007699681","data":{"timestamp":" 947007699681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007711182","data":{"timestamp":" 947007711182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007723272","data":{"timestamp":" 947007723272"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007735798","data":{"timestamp":" 947007735798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007747978","data":{"timestamp":" 947007747978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007759162","data":{"timestamp":" 947007759162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007769989","data":{"timestamp":" 947007769989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007778747","data":{"timestamp":" 947007778747"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007793827","data":{"timestamp":" 947007793827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007806700","data":{"timestamp":" 947007806700"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007817521","data":{"timestamp":" 947007817521"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007830214","data":{"timestamp":" 947007830214"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007842594","data":{"timestamp":" 947007842594"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007856502","data":{"timestamp":" 947007856502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007892209","data":{"timestamp":" 947007892209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007905708","data":{"timestamp":" 947007905708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007920677","data":{"timestamp":" 947007920677"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007932532","data":{"timestamp":" 947007932532"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007963966","data":{"timestamp":" 947007963966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007973250","data":{"timestamp":" 947007973250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007982250","data":{"timestamp":" 947007982250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007995360","data":{"timestamp":" 947007995360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007998597","data":{"timestamp":" 947007998597"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" af04f62f-fe41-4280-b1c4-774d036bd9dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008003872","data":{"timestamp":" 947008003872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" a21d755e-d4b4-4119-9fc8-81732a499c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008015424","data":{"timestamp":" 947008015423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" a21d755e-d4b4-4119-9fc8-81732a499c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008015501","data":{"timestamp":" 947008015501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" a21d755e-d4b4-4119-9fc8-81732a499c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008023022","data":{"timestamp":" 947008023022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" dbe703d0-93e9-47d9-bd3f-9f5bf87e7943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008054485","data":{"timestamp":" 947008054484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" dbe703d0-93e9-47d9-bd3f-9f5bf87e7943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008057127","data":{"timestamp":" 947008057125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" dbe703d0-93e9-47d9-bd3f-9f5bf87e7943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008057271","data":{"timestamp":" 947008057271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" dbe703d0-93e9-47d9-bd3f-9f5bf87e7943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008066475","data":{"timestamp":" 947008066475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008070349","data":{"timestamp":" 947008070349"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008074564","data":{"timestamp":" 947008074564"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008080059","data":{"timestamp":" 947008080059"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008085989","data":{"timestamp":" 947008085989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008095223","data":{"timestamp":" 947008095222"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008098078","data":{"timestamp":" 947008098078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 3b04d2d2-0085-4bdf-abf5-a385ae5dfa08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008167723","data":{"timestamp":" 947008167723"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008233227","data":{"timestamp":" 947008233227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008270257","data":{"timestamp":" 947008270257"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008272462","data":{"timestamp":" 947008272462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008274643","data":{"timestamp":" 947008274642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008276873","data":{"timestamp":" 947008276873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008381732","data":{"timestamp":" 947008381731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008381807","data":{"timestamp":" 947008381807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARUJI"," userResponse":" SARUJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008390760","data":{"timestamp":" 947008390759"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008420167","data":{"timestamp":" 947008420167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 8667c34c-4456-4da8-aed7-8c9e3cf30c45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008429085","data":{"timestamp":" 947008429085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" cffee7d2-9103-4425-8a1b-aeb18b994784"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008431145","data":{"timestamp":" 947008431145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" cffee7d2-9103-4425-8a1b-aeb18b994784"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008433223","data":{"timestamp":" 947008433223"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" cffee7d2-9103-4425-8a1b-aeb18b994784"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008435114","data":{"timestamp":" 947008435113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" cffee7d2-9103-4425-8a1b-aeb18b994784"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008435174","data":{"timestamp":" 947008435174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" cffee7d2-9103-4425-8a1b-aeb18b994784"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008446560","data":{"timestamp":" 947008446560"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008448620","data":{"timestamp":" 947008448620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008450724","data":{"timestamp":" 947008450724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008453955","data":{"timestamp":" 947008453954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008456202","data":{"timestamp":" 947008456201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008458408","data":{"timestamp":" 947008458408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008461479","data":{"timestamp":" 947008461478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008463661","data":{"timestamp":" 947008463659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008465911","data":{"timestamp":" 947008465911"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008469177","data":{"timestamp":" 947008469176"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008471285","data":{"timestamp":" 947008471284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008473376","data":{"timestamp":" 947008473376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008476374","data":{"timestamp":" 947008476373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008478565","data":{"timestamp":" 947008478565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008480743","data":{"timestamp":" 947008480743"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008483790","data":{"timestamp":" 947008483789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008486161","data":{"timestamp":" 947008486161"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008488497","data":{"timestamp":" 947008488497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008491541","data":{"timestamp":" 947008491541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008493691","data":{"timestamp":" 947008493691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008495822","data":{"timestamp":" 947008495822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008498867","data":{"timestamp":" 947008498867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008500982","data":{"timestamp":" 947008500981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008503094","data":{"timestamp":" 947008503094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008506181","data":{"timestamp":" 947008506180"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008508549","data":{"timestamp":" 947008508549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008510964","data":{"timestamp":" 947008510964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008514046","data":{"timestamp":" 947008514046"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008516316","data":{"timestamp":" 947008516316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008518579","data":{"timestamp":" 947008518579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008521591","data":{"timestamp":" 947008521590"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008523866","data":{"timestamp":" 947008523866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008526071","data":{"timestamp":" 947008526071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008528986","data":{"timestamp":" 947008528986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008531319","data":{"timestamp":" 947008531318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008533720","data":{"timestamp":" 947008533719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008536898","data":{"timestamp":" 947008536898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008539265","data":{"timestamp":" 947008539264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008541631","data":{"timestamp":" 947008541631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008544572","data":{"timestamp":" 947008544572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008546823","data":{"timestamp":" 947008546823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008549093","data":{"timestamp":" 947008549093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008552335","data":{"timestamp":" 947008552335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008554619","data":{"timestamp":" 947008554618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008556895","data":{"timestamp":" 947008556895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008560289","data":{"timestamp":" 947008560288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008562754","data":{"timestamp":" 947008562753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008565155","data":{"timestamp":" 947008565155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008568041","data":{"timestamp":" 947008568040"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008570245","data":{"timestamp":" 947008570245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008572373","data":{"timestamp":" 947008572373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008575731","data":{"timestamp":" 947008575730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008577997","data":{"timestamp":" 947008577996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008580276","data":{"timestamp":" 947008580275"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008583309","data":{"timestamp":" 947008583308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008585524","data":{"timestamp":" 947008585524"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008587737","data":{"timestamp":" 947008587736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008590718","data":{"timestamp":" 947008590717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008592816","data":{"timestamp":" 947008592815"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008594892","data":{"timestamp":" 947008594892"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008597935","data":{"timestamp":" 947008597935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008600121","data":{"timestamp":" 947008600121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008602306","data":{"timestamp":" 947008602305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008605436","data":{"timestamp":" 947008605436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008607632","data":{"timestamp":" 947008607631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008609876","data":{"timestamp":" 947008609875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008613160","data":{"timestamp":" 947008613159"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008615490","data":{"timestamp":" 947008615489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008617845","data":{"timestamp":" 947008617844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008620979","data":{"timestamp":" 947008620978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008623276","data":{"timestamp":" 947008623276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008625559","data":{"timestamp":" 947008625559"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008628933","data":{"timestamp":" 947008628932"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008629011","data":{"timestamp":" 947008629008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008671160","data":{"timestamp":" 947008671159"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 1e98794c-7ad2-4608-9e50-a25c85fe74e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008671243","data":{"timestamp":" 947008671242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" 01d19e67-e1ee-41a7-963e-acddd63c5356"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008725180","data":{"timestamp":" 947008725179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" f7826896-1be0-4f70-9c6a-0c0f493120ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-a-t"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008763781","data":{"timestamp":" 947008763781"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" f7826896-1be0-4f70-9c6a-0c0f493120ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_r-o-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947008769962","data":{"timestamp":" 947008769962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_203548"," gameId":" f7826896-1be0-4f70-9c6a-0c0f493120ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-h-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}